What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Real estate.
And how long have you been in the business for?
Oh, 15 years.
Over these 15 years, what has
been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
So this year, our business is gonna do
north of $20 million.
$22 million.
Better yet, in one month.
Most I've made in one month was, what, 80 grand?
And Wall Street is a beast.
It's a savage beast, this business, it's savage.
Look to your left, look to your right.
The guy that, they're all gonna be gone
in a couple of months, they're all gonna be gone.
How old are you now?
I'm 48 and a half.
I'm 33.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I would say in my 40s.
Have you ever been broke before?
Absolutely.
Oh, absolutely.
Many times.
When I got into real estate,
I had like less than $4,000.
How can somebody become a millionaire in 2024?
Let me say this real quick,
because I know one 20-year-old's gonna get it.
New York City is the number
one city in the entire world
with the most millionaires.
And since we're in the Big Apple,
I'm gonna be going all over,
asking the most successful New York City entrepreneurs
how they became wealthy and
how you can start your path
to becoming financial.
And financially free in 2024.
So with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Better yet, in one month.
Most I've made in one month was what?
80 grand?
80 grand in one month.
Yeah, one month.
Yeah, that was my best month.
And Wall Street is a beast.
It's a savage beast.
This business is savage.
Look to your left, look to your right.
The guy that they're all gonna
be gone in a couple of months.
They're all gonna be gone in a couple of months.
They're all gonna be gone.
What was the turning point
in your life getting into finance?
Did you always know you were gonna pursue this business?
No, absolutely not.
I was a personal trainer in a gym.
Long story short, the guy who I was training,
he thought I'd be good in this business.
And that was over 17, 18 years ago.
And here I am.
Finance is very competitive.
How did you stand out?
Discipline.
Most people can't say no to themselves.
They gotta have that drink.
They gotta have that party.
They gotta have that girlfriend.
They gotta have that sex.
And all that right there attributes to poverty
because it drains you of all your resources.
Your number one resource is your energy.
That's it.
Number one resource is your energy.
And it's a natural.
It's a natural commodity.
If you're prodigal with that and you're wasteful with that,
then you can't accumulate anything.
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh, absolutely.
Many times.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I would say in my 40s.
When it comes to the
way that people look at money,
what would you say is the number one thing
that separates the middle class
from those who end up building that wealth?
Spending habits.
It's like people hate money, right?
They gotta get rid of it.
I gotta go buy.
I gotta keep up with the Joneses.
The money's a frequency
and you have to get on the money frequency.
Like radio stations, TV stations.
Like if you wanna watch CNBC, right?
You gotta tune to that channel.
You can't go to ABC to
pick up frequency from CNBC, right?
So the content of that
channel you have to tune to.
Money is a station, no different.
So you have to tune to the consciousness of money.
When you tune to the consciousness of money,
then you get fed all the information necessary
for you to accumulate wealth.
Then you become magnetized.
You become a money magnet
and you no longer have to chase it.
See, we're taught to chase money.
That's the worst thing you could teach somebody.
You don't chase money.
You become magnetized money-wise and money chases you.
You never chase money.
Just like women, you never chase anything.
All right, guys.
Thank you so much for your time.
So I really appreciate that.
Have a great day.
So since we're in New York City,
you know I had to go down to Wall Street
to find a Wall Street beast.
And that guy became a millionaire in his 40s.
But what did he say was the number one thing
that separated him apart in finance?
It's his discipline.
At the end of the day,
if you can't take care of yourself,
you're never gonna be able
to take care of your finances.
So that's a great interview.
Let's go get this next one.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
The acai bowl smoothie franchise industry.
And how long have you been an entrepreneur for?
My whole life.
I started selling candy and goodies
when I was seven years old in school.
Started a power washing company when
I was 14 with my buddy.
So I've been doing it my whole life.
What?
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
So this year,
our business is gonna do north of $20 million.
$20 million?
Yeah.
What was the turning point like getting into this business?
Did you always know that you were gonna pursue
the food and beverage, you know, that type of business?
Or like, how did you end up in this business?
I'll be honest.
I started off as a broker on Wall Street.
I did not think I was
gonna get into food and beverage,
but I saw an opportunity.
It was an opportunity at the time
to jump into a market that there
was a lot of white space in.
So that's where I saw the opportunity
and that's where I jumped in full force.
Yeah.
You worked on Wall Street for a while.
What's the greatest lesson about money
that you learned throughout your time on Wall Street?
So I learned this myself.
When it comes to business, you wanna think very long-term.
When it comes to Wall Street investing in stocks,
bonds, companies, crypto,
you wanna think a little bit more short-term.
When you set a goal for what you wanna see
in terms of a return, pull it 30%.
When you hit those goals, sell.
You know, a lot of the younger kids today,
they think to the moon
that everything's gonna just keep
going up and up and up.
That's not the case.
It's usually greater fool theory.
So set a benchmark and get out.
How old are you now?
I'm 33.
How old were you?
When you became a millionaire?
About 30.
30 years old.
Yeah.
Have you ever been broke before?
Absolutely.
So it came from a middle-class family,
but when I was working on Wall Street,
I was making two grand a
month for over a year, two years,
and I was just scraping by,
decided to pull the ripcord
and follow my passion in an industry
that I felt a little
bit more of a connection to,
but was broke many times throughout the years.
What was the number one book that changed your life?
For anyone who owns a business,
I would recommend Traction by Gino Wickman.
Phenomenal book.
What was the best financial decision
that you made throughout your career?
I bet on myself.
Yeah?
Yep.
How important is it to take that risk
and go all in for yourself?
It's not the best choice for everybody.
I think some people are,
they need the structure of working for a company
or working for someone that
has the answers in that space.
For me, I knew that I
had to follow my own path.
So I think the biggest piece of advice is
be okay with who you are naturally.
Don't force being an entrepreneur or any other route.
If entrepreneur is here, then you have to follow it.
Thank you so much for your time.
Brother, thank you for having me.
I really appreciate it.
His business is going to do $20 million this fall.
But what I found amazing about that interview
wasn't just the advice that he gave,
but the fact that he
is in the food and beverage
in the acai bowl industry.
It just goes to show that
even with the most unique idea,
you can make millions and millions of dollars, man.
You just got to put your
mind to it and make it happen.
Great interview.
Let's go get this next one.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Real estate.
And how long have you been in the business for?
Oh, 15 years.
Over these 15 years,
what has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year?
2021, I made $22 million.
$22 million.
As an eight-figure entrepreneur,
what's been the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your career?
Jay-Z said, scared money don't make money.
And you have to invest for the long-term.
You know, you have Warren Buffett talks about compounding,
you know, and that's really, really important.
So every dollar you put in,
you're pulling out, you know, 10X, 20X, 100X,
but it's not going to be tomorrow.
It's going to be over that lifespan.
I mean, 15 years is a long time.
What was the turning point like getting into this industry?
Did you always know you're going to pursue real estate
or how did you end up here?
No, I moved to New York
City in 2006 to do theater
and I totally ran out of all my money.
And then it was become a bartender, become a waiter,
become a temp, figure out, go back to school
or get my real estate license and pay my bills.
I had to make like $2,000 a month.
If I could do 2000 bucks a month,
I could stay in New York
City and that's what I did.
And I got started the day Lehman Brothers
filed for bankruptcy.
Right.
What's the greatest lesson that you've learned
about real estate?
If there's one lesson that you pass on to someone
about to start off in
the real estate business in 2024,
what would that be?
Riches in niches, right?
That's super important.
Like you pick your niche
and you just go for it.
And then endurance.
Endurance for the win.
Because a lot of people
will hop from kind of niche
to niche to niche and then it doesn't work out
and they see that it doesn't work out
and they see that as a brick wall
instead of what it really is,
which is just a speed bump.
What's been the most amount
of money worth of real estate
that you've sold in a single year?
This year we'll do probably four and a half billion
in sales this year.
Yeah, but I mean, you have to understand
like we sell entire buildings, right?
Like we're selling Mercedes-Benz in Miami right now.
That's a $1.4 billion sellout, you know?
And I'll sell it and I mean,
I'm going to try to
sell it all in a year.
Maybe it'll take me a little bit longer.
Most expensive single home I've ever sold.
I did, it was a couple different structures,
but to like one person residentially was 195 million
and I did it in two days.
How many billionaires have you met throughout your life?
What's the greatest lesson that you've learned
from networking with billionaires?
They really understand the value of a dollar,
which means they don't second guess spending it
when it makes sense,
but they also are super,
super cheap when it makes sense
because they understand what it took to get there
and they value their time more than anything.
I made a video about it,
about it.
I made a video about it once,
but I'd say almost a handful of billionaires
that have gone to dinner with,
because we do closing dinners and things.
You go to a nice restaurant,
they have no time to look at the menu, right?
They just say, bring me your best
because they just don't care, right?
Unless they have a dietary restriction, you know?
But most billionaires I know
actually don't have dietary restrictions.
It's everyone else that has dietary restrictions.
How old are you now?
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
28, somewhere like that.
How can somebody become a millionaire in 2024?
Learn how to sell.
Like sales is the greatest
skill set of the new economy,
because I think,
the rest of us who are
pushed to go into student debt,
to go to college,
to not figure out how to pay it off,
to get a W2 job that's 9 to 5,
to get a picket fence and have 2.2 kids.
I think that that dream
was sold to us really hard
and I don't think it's real anymore, right?
And it's really not.
So for you to work for yourself,
have 10 streams of income,
doing whatever you want,
whenever you want,
however you want,
like that is the greatest future that you can have,
but you have to learn how to do it.
It's a muscle.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thanks.
I appreciate you, brother.
We just interviewed Ryan Serhan,
who made $22 million this last year in real estate.
If you know anything about real estate,
you know exactly who Ryan Serhan is.
And just like he said,
scared money does not make money.
The most successful people are willing to risk it all.
But guys,
I have a very special announcement for you.
We are going to interview Gary Vee,
otherwise known as Gary Vanderchuk,
one of the most successful marketing entrepreneurs
in the entire world.
If you know entrepreneurship,
you know who Gary Vee is.
So with that being said,
let's go see what Gary has to say.
How old are you now?
I'm 48 and a half.
48 and a half.
If you were to go back in time
and have a conversation with your 20-year-old self
when you were starting from zero,
what's the best piece of advice
that you would give to your younger self?
That everything that you believe in intuitively
is 100% right.
And that the only flaw you have
is your inability to be candorous
to people that you love in work.
And you're going to need to figure that out
because that's your kryptonite.
And once you get that right,
you got it.
And so what I mean to everybody,
Jaylen, you, all of you,
is most kids listen to
other people that look like me
instead of listening to themselves.
You all know better than I know.
You know yourself.
And most people talk
themselves out of what they know in their stomach
and they use their brain
or even worse, outside fucking voices,
even if they're well-intended and awesome.
What I talk about is right,
but it's right for people
that are more wired like me.
It's not right for everyone.
And so what I would
tell every 20-year-old on Earth is
stop listening to fucking other people.
People you put on a pedestal,
your fucking mom and dad,
teachers, mentors.
It's all good.
Take it in.
But you fucking know your answer.
Last one for you.
You've scaled a massive nine-figure business.
A lot of entrepreneurs, they'll have a great idea.
They'll start that business.
They struggle to scale and grow.
What's been your secret to scaling?
Have you been able
to build this thing out to the massive company
that it is today?
I'm willing to eat shit
in a way that you kids don't want to.
Lack of patience, entitlement at scale,
giving a fuck about other people thinking you're successful
versus being successful.
I'm willing to eat shit, bro.
Do you know what entrepreneurship is?
What's that?
Losing constantly with an occasional win.
This shit is not fun.
This is fighting.
This shit's fighting.
You get punched in the fucking face,
but it's the best if you're a fighter.
You understand?
Yeah.
But the problem is now everybody thinks it's cool
to be a fighter.
When they might not be a fighter.
Let me say this real quick
because I know one 20 year
old is going to get it
and it's going to change your life
and I can't wait to see
you at the airport in 11 years
and be like that was the video.
Do you know how much money
the number three at Facebook made?
How much?
Billions.
Everybody wants to be a number one,
but not everyone was built to be a number one.
There's no embarrassment of not being a number one.
The number three at the biggest companies in the world
will make more than 99.99999999% of number ones.
And so just don't put this shit on a pedestal.
Everything is great if it's who you actually are.
Man, you guys.
We just interviewed
Gary Vee one of the most
iconic figures in all of entrepreneurship
and absolute legend.
But guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
Be sure to like and subscribe for
amazing content on the way coming very soon
and click the link in the description
below to subscribe to the Hard Knocks newsletter
because we're sending out weekly updates insights
and lessons from the world's
top entrepreneurs and business owners.
You don't want to miss out on it.
So subscribe to the Hard Knocks newsletter right now.
With that being said, we'll see
you guys in the next video.
Click here to watch our full video
going all over Las Vegas asking multimillionaires
how you can start your path
to becoming financially free in 2024.
We'll see you guys in the next video.